[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Do you want them to take it better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "No, I didn't want them to take it badly in the first place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Too easy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "That's what they call a home run, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Do you have a moral code yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What's your litmus test?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, you can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "But what are we meant to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "For a very long time, you would never have imagined being in Hollywood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "What is the reality of Hollywood excess?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Is it to not be famous too early?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Is it a lot easier, is my point, to be older and become famous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Well, I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"], "LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "It's the I can't believe my luck that I get up in the morning, have an idea, and I can start writing that idea and it will get made at the moment, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "What I can't believe is the way you look, because we all fell in love back in Britain with fat, chubby Ricky.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Not much at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Hollywood smiley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "``", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Do you get more groupies now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I don't -- never got groupies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 265, "question": "A svelte comedic auteur or as a chubby loser?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "History of television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "\"Seinfeld,\" lovely show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "You love Twitter, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Why do you like it so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I like it for lots of reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What were you getting at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, you know, as a comedian --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", ":"], "qSentId": 362, "question": "-- you'd fit in well looking like that?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, I thought I looked intellectual there --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Always?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How does your -- how does your atheism, which you're passionate about -- how does that play with your American audience, given that so many people in America are God-fearing people, and probably take exception to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, but they shouldn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Do I do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Should we play you what Steve Carell said about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Yes, please.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 492, "question": "But you could play a Ricky Gervais character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Perhaps, but to actually go in front of people and --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "-- you're all heart, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Do you like Steve Carell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "He's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Carell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "What, with -- romantic love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "IN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I'm assuming women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Why haven't you married her yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Well, we are, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Oh, I'd never say never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How do you show your romantic side?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "It would be professional, really -- a moment in your life, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "There's loads of things whizzing through my head, but they're all from childhood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "I just remembered one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "Steve, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Steve.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "You appeared how many times on Johnny Carson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "About 140 times.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Carson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "That has to be a record, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "Yes, Bob Hope was the most, and I was the second most.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Carousel"], "PERSON": ["Charlie Hartsock", "Vance DeGeneres"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", ":", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "What was the idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Well, Charlie Hartsock and Vance DeGeneres, who are my partners at Carousel, had this idea to kind of trace the -- trace comedy in terms of generations and -- and how it cross-pollinates and sort of look to people's inspirations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "-- of superstar comedians, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 698, "question": "How are you -- how are you billing it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Well, I -- I don't know if it's a definitive history of comedy, but it is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "On what makes people laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "It's unique in the way in which the comedians talk about what they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "That happened between you and him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "That never happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Is there a stat -- when you all get together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "It's so subjective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 778, "question": "But biggest comedian wasn't your great burning ambition as a kid, was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJS", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 779, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "And if it's funny, then, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "Let's talk a little break, gents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "But you do -- do you thank God every day that these things happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Larry"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "It's a little bit like that, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "There -- there is no Moe and Larry here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 874, "question": "It will hide your own lack of character, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 875, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Arkin"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 879, "question": "Who -- if I could trap you both on a desert island separately and you could have one comedian with you to make you laugh for the rest of your days, who would you take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 880, "answer": "I would take Alan Arkin.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 881, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 882, "answer": "Because he makes -- one-to-one, he makes me laugh more than anyone I've ever met.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 883, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 884, "answer": "He is -- he's so dry and so acerbic, he just -- I love being around the man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Groucho"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 885, "question": "Who would you take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 886, "answer": "I'd probably take Groucho.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "If you're honest, did you prefer life before, when you were more anonymous, or have you actually embraced the whole fame thing with great enthusiasm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "It's much, much better to be rich and famous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "I like to think it might have been, but you never know, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "It's a lot tougher to deal with, I think, if you get that kind of thing when you're younger.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "Do you miss the character?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 969, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 970, "answer": "Oh, not in a million years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 972, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 973, "answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 990, "question": "You've got seven movies on the go, is that right, over the next two years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 991, "answer": "And I'm writing a symphony and I have a cooking show coming up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 993, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 994, "answer": "Did you ever imagine here you'd be in Hollywood in your smart power suit, in the middle of a seven movie extravaganza --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 996, "question": "-- earning you, potentially, a billion dollars?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 997, "answer": "A billion dollars.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1001, "question": "You must pinch yourself a bit, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1002, "answer": "I'm always pinching myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1027, "question": "You need to have had cigarettes burned on you for years, don't you, to be genuinely -- to make an audience laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1028, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]